<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Careerlogy</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="student_instruction">If you are students, you need to identify which <a href="https://careerlogy.com/Careerlogy/uploads/Entrepreneurship_Intro.docx"> problem (list attached) </a> (there are three category) you are facing namely academic (related with study), psychological and physiological. Further, these categories are divided into specific categories. You have to select one of those and write down your question (problem, challenges, and key issues) and you will get answer. Further, there may be a neurological view of your question, which explained through link in the answer. \n • If you are not able to identify your question in the category please feel free to give as feedback in our suggestion box. \n • Also if you are not satisfied by our answer please feel free to give as feedback in our suggestion box.\n\n <font fgcolor='#FFEF5350'><b>WORD OF CAUTION</b></font> – it will be great on your part, if you have confidence, with the help of answer you can resolve your questions.\n Otherwise you need to take help of professional <a href="https://careerlogy.com/Careerlogy/uploads/Entrepreneurship_Intro.docx">experts (list attached)</a> which we have mentioned in the answer. </string>
    <string name="entrepreneur_instruction">if you are entrepreneur or wish to start entrepreneurship, you need to identify <a href="https://careerlogy.com/Careerlogy/uploads/Entrepreneurship_Intro.docx"> problem (list attached) </a>     • facing namely personal, organisational, industry. Further, these categories are divided into specific categories. You have to select one of those and write down your question (problem, challenges, and key issues) and you will get answer. Further, there may be a neurological view of your question, which explained through link in the answer.
    • If you are not able to identify your questions in the category please feel free to give as feedback in our suggestion box.
    •  Also if you are not satisfied by our answer please feel free to give as feedback in our suggestion box.\n\n <font fgcolor='#FFEF5350'><b>WORD OF CAUTION</b></font> – it will be great on your part, if you have confidence, with the help of answer you can resolve your questions.\n Otherwise you need to take help of professional <a href="https://careerlogy.com/Careerlogy/uploads/Entrepreneurship_Intro.docx">experts (list attached)</a> which we have mentioned in the answer. </string>
    <string name="disclamer">“WE ARE AT THE BEGINNING OF A NEW ERA OF CAREER CHOICES” \n\n“CAREER INTELLECT TEST” was created by our team through case studies, own experience, workshops, surveys and interviews with various segments of experts in education and business industry.\n\nThe career intellect is powerful tool to understand and influence your career either employment or entrepreneurship and various professional role required in organisation.\n\nThe basic concept behind above test is how your brain is comfortable at various aspects of human being such as behaviours, actions, interactions with others, decision making, internal state, internal process, how you are paying attention to various things and how you are adapting changes.\n\nThere are some activities you do, where you are completely comfortable. These activities are very much essential for the overall growth and development of your organisation, where you are working or it is owned by you.\n\nThese test is design considering the various parts, function and features of brain. Over a period of time because nature or nurture (parents, school, area), there are probability that your actual intellect may get hidden or succumb (even if you do testing through eeg machine.) \n\nThe test is intended for educational purposes only and should not be understood to establish any type of diagnosis or healthcare recommendation.\n\n<c><b>WHAT WILL HAPPEN, WHEN YOU IDENTIFY YOUR INTELLECT AT EARLY AGE AT SCHOOL/COLLEGE AND YOU START DEVELOPING YOUR POTENTIAL ALONG WITH YOUR EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION!</b></c></string>
</resources>
